所以每一个现代浏览器
So every modern browser
包含一组工具，
contains a set of tools,
这使我们作为开发人员的生活变得更加轻松。
which makes our lives as developers a lot easier.
我们将这些工具统称为
And we call these tools collectively
开发人员工具或简称开发工具。
developer tools or for short dev tools.
所以在这次讲座中，
And so in this lecture,
让我们学习如何使用
let's learn how to use
谷歌浏览器开发工具。
the Google Chrome Dev Tools.
让我们给自己
And let's give ourselves
这里有更多的空间开始。
some more space here to start.
现在有三种方式
And now there are three ways
打开开发者工具。
to open up the developer tools.
所以首先，你可以右键单击
So first, you can right click
页面上的任何位置
anywhere on the page
然后单击检查或检查元素。
and then click inspect or inspect element.
所以这些是开发工具，
So these are the dev tools,
但让我首先向您展示另外两种方式。
but let me first show you two other ways.
第二种方式是来这里
The second way is to come here
到视图菜单，然后是开发人员，
to the view menu, then developer,
然后是这里的开发者工具。
and then here developer tools.
好的。
All right.
或者第三种方式是捷径
Or the third way is a shortcut
在键盘上，那是选项命令
on the keyboard and that is option command
或 Windows I 上的选项控制。
or option control on Windows I.
好的。
All right.
然后我们会想来这里
And then we will want to come here
到第一个标签，上面写着元素。
to the very first tab, which says, elements.
把它放大一点
Just make this a bit bigger
所以你实际上可以看到它。
so you can actually see it.
好的。
All right.
所以我们可以在这里看到的第一件事
So the first thing that we can see here
在元素选项卡中是确切的 HTML
in the elements tab is the exact HTML
我们在 HTML 文档中编写的。
that we wrote in our HTML documents.
对？
Right?
所以在这里我们可以打开每个元素
So here we can open up each element
通过点击它们。
by clicking on them.
然后当我们悬停它们时，
And then as we hover them,
他们实际上在这里突出显示
they actually get highlighted here
在页面上，或者它可能非常有帮助。
on the page or it can be very helpful.
所以你会看到，例如，
So you'll see, for example,
我们的标题是整个盒子
that our header is this entire box
我们在此处以蓝色突出显示。
that we see highlighted here in blue.
对？
Right?
就是这样，然后导航就是这一切。
So that's this then the navigation is all this.
如果我们打开它，
And if we open it,
然后每个链接
then each of these links
就是这个很小的盒子吗
is just this very small box here
并肩坐在这里，
and there sitting here side by side,
正如我们所见。
as we can see.
对？
Right?
所以这是第一件事
So that is the first thing
我们可以在这里探索。
that we can explore here.
然后第二件事，
And then the second thing,
更重要的是，
and even more important,
是左侧的样式选项卡。
is the style tab here on the left side.
所以在这里我们可以看到所有的样式
So here we can see all the styles
已应用于特定元素。
that have been applied to a certain element.
所以让我们以H1为例，在这里，
So let's go to the H1 for example, here,
然后我们可以点击它。
and then we can click it.
然后在左边，
And then here on the left side,
当前的所有样式
all the styles that are currently
应用于我们的 CSS 文件中的这个元素
applied to this element in our CSS file
在这里显示。
are displayed here.
所以我们在代码的某个地方有这个规则，
So we have this rule somewhere in our code,
将字体设置为 26
which sets the font of 26
并完成所有这些。
and does all of this.
对。
Right.
然后我们在某个地方也有这个规则，
Then we also have this rule somewhere,
设置颜色。
which sets the color.
事实上，这里就是这个。
And in fact it is this one here.
对？
Right?
所以第一个就是这个。
So this first one is this.
然后在这里我们得到这个。
Then here we get this one.
最后，这里还有这个。
And finally, there's also this one here.
对？
Right?
所以这正是这个。
And so that is exactly this one.
好的。
Okay.
现在也许你以前想知道
Now maybe you had wondered before
为什么这里的文字实际上是粗体的
00:03:20,180 -->00:03:21,960
在这个 H1 元素中，
why the text here is actually bold
in this H1 element,
以及这样做的原因
and the reason for that
基本上是默认样式。
is basically the default style.
所以H1的那些默认样式
So those default styles for the H1
是此规则中显示的内容
are what are displayed here in this rule
用户代理样式表。
of the user agent style sheet.
所以这只是一个花哨的词
So that's just a fancy word
基本上是默认样式。
for basically the default style.
而在这里，
And down here,
我们可以看到字体粗细
we can see that the font weight
默认设置为粗体。
is set to bold by default.
好的。
Okay.
那么这里的这个是东西
Then this one here is something
我们很快就会知道。
that we will learn about very soon.
所以暂时不用担心。
So don't worry about it for now.
然后在这里，让我们看看，
And then here, let's see,
例如，这些链接。
for example, these links.
所以这里是他们的代码。
And so here is the code for them.
所以我们已经应用到它们的 CSS，
So the CSS that we had applied to them already,
所以颜色和文字装饰。
so the color and the text decoration.
对？
Right?
但是现在如果我们真的想要
But now what if we actually wanted
在此处添加更多样式。
to add some more styles here.
所以我们实际上可以这样做。
So we could actually do that.
所以当然只是为了测试目的，
So just for testing purposes of course,
我们现在可以添加一个字体大小，比方说，
we could now add a font size, let's say,
30像素，
of 30 pixels,
然后立即在页面上的所有链接。
and then immediately all the links on the page.
所以不只是这个，
So not just this one,
还有这个和其他的，
but also this one and the other ones,
它们现在都将具有字体大小，
all of them will now have the font size,
全部 30 个像素。
all 30 pixels.
为了测试它，我们可以打开和关闭它。
And to test that, we can then turn it on and off.
当然我们也可以
And of course we can also
打开和关闭其他样式
turn the other styles on and off
只需点击这里。
simply by clicking here.
好的。
All right.
当然，我们在这里指定的这些值，
And of course these values that we specify here,
它们不会影响最终网站。
they will not affect the final website.
所以我们的代码不会改变
So our code does not get changed
如果我们这样做
if we do this
我们可以很容易地证明
and we can prove that by very easily
重新加载页面
reload the page
然后一切恢复正常。
and then everything is back to normal.
好的。
All right.
但这实际上是在探索
But that's actually exploring
链接多一点，
links a little bit more,
因为我们可以做一些很酷的事情。
because there's something cool that we can do.
所以现在只有
So right now, there is only
此处应用了此 CSS 规则。
this CSS rule here applied.
所以只有一个具有链接伪类的。
So only the one that has the link pseudo class.
那是因为现在，
And that's because of right now,
链接未悬停或未激活。
the link is not being hovered or it's not active.
因此，
And so therefore,
该样式不适用。
the style for that does not apply.
然而，点击这里，
However, by clicking here,
我们基本上可以伪造这些状态之一。
we can basically fake one of these states.
所以我们可以，例如，
So we can, for example,
假装链接当前被悬停。
fake that the link is currently being hovered.
因此，如果我们在悬停时单击此处，
So if we click here on hover,
然后你看到现在这个规则在这里
then you see that now this rule here
正在申请，因为现在 A
is applying, because now A
与伪类悬停确实存在。
with the pseudo class hover does actually exist.
所以让我们在页面上看到它。
So let's see that on the page.
应该有状态的那个
And the one that should have the state
是我在这里实际选择的那个。
is the one that I actually have selected here.
所以这是我选择的，
So this is the one that I selected,
所以这是一个
and so this is the one
现在看起来好像它正在盘旋，
that now looks as if it is being hovered,
即使不是。
even though it is not.
所以这很棒。
And so this is great.
所以我们可以测试我们的网页
So we can test our webpage
实际上不必手动去那里
without actually having to manually go there
并将鼠标悬停在链接上。
and hover over the links.
好的。
Okay.
当然，我们可以在这里为这个做同样的事情.
Of course we can do the same for this one here.
我们可以继续在这里搜索
And we could go ahead and search that here
在 HTML 树中，
in the HTML tree,
但我发现简单地右键单击更容易
but I find it easier to simply right click
在我想要的元素上然后检查。
on the element that I want and then inspect.
然后自动移动到那里。
And so that then automatically moves there.
所以如果我现在点击悬停，
So if I click on hover now,
然后它自动变成悬停，
then it automatically becomes hover,
即使它不是真的。
even though it's not really.
当然，对于主动来说也是如此。
And the same of course, for active.
对？
Right?
所以它是活跃的，
So it's active,
但我们也希望它看起来
but we also want it to look
就像它同时盘旋一样，
like it's hovered at the same time,
因为通常当它处于活动状态时，
because usually when it's active,
它也悬停。
it is also hovered.
但无论如何，
But anyway,
重要的是现在我们有了
what matters is that now we have
所有这些规则都适用于这一刻。
all these rules here applying in this moment.
好的。
All right.
但现在让我们再次将其关闭。
But now let's turn it off again.
是的，
And yeah,
我想这实际上就是我必须向你展示的全部内容
I think that's actually all I had to show you
在此刻。
at this point.
所以我们将使用开发工具
So we're going to use the dev tools
在整个课程的剩余时间里，
all the time throughout the rest of the course,
因为这些是绝对必要的
because these are absolutely essential
以有效的方式创建网站。
to create a website in an efficient way.
所以我真的很兴奋
So I was actually really excited
当我发现自己
when I found out myself
关于这些工具
about these tools
我希望你也喜欢它们。
and I hope you liked them as well.
而你，也许继续尝试
And that you, maybe go ahead and experiment
现在有点左右。
around a little bit with this now.
所以你可以点击任何元素
So you can just click on any element
你喜欢和实验的
that you'd like and experiment
也许有点转弯
maybe a little bit with turning
这些风格的开启和关闭，
these styles on and off,
也许添加一些其他的。
maybe adding some other ones.
它真的有点分析
And it's really analyzing a bit
这里发生了什么
what happens here
应用所有这些不同的规则。
with all these different rules being applied.
所以玩得开心点。
So have some fun with that.
我很快就会在下一个视频中见到你。
And I see you soon in the next video.